<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blevins Updates on The Blevins</title>
    <link>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blevins Updates on The Blevins</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Help! We have a freshman and a middle-schooler!</title>
      <link>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2018/09/27/help-we-have-a-freshman-and-a-middle-schooler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2018/09/27/help-we-have-a-freshman-and-a-middle-schooler/</guid>
      <description>22-year missions adventure This month marks 22 years ago that we went into missions and started our Youth with an Mission adventure.
An incredible missionary adventure with God, an adventure in faith and trust, an adventure across borders, an adventure in being dependent on donations, an adventure in wonderful provision, blessings and testimonies. 22 years of missions made possible, in part, by you!
 First missions trip to Uganda in 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;I felt completely heard and understood&#34;</title>
      <link>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2018/05/17/i-felt-completely-heard-and-understood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2018/05/17/i-felt-completely-heard-and-understood/</guid>
      <description>The last week of April and the first week of May, seven participants came for the &amp;ldquo;Radiant Life&amp;rdquo; Debriefing retreat for missionary families, couples and singles in Orlando. This was a period of rest, refreshment and renewal for these missionaries. Here are just a couple of powerful testimonies from participants in the Radiant Life debriefing retreat in Orlando, Florida:
&amp;ldquo;What a week! Our family spent the last 9 days in Florida attending a missionary debrief conference “Radiant Life” through Excelling Leaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missionaries not just surviving, but thriving!</title>
      <link>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2018/02/26/missionaries-not-just-surviving-but-thriving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2018/02/26/missionaries-not-just-surviving-but-thriving/</guid>
      <description>International Member Care Consultation (IMCC) A couple weeks ago Jolanda attended the International Member Care Consultation (IMCC) at YWAM Orlando, FL. Together with YWAM Member Care workers from the Caribbean, East and South East Asia, Europe, North America, South America and Africa they came together to reconnect, receive teaching, and do a lot of networking. It was a great opportunity to learn about the different training models/courses and internships for member care workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipping Kingdom Workers</title>
      <link>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2017/11/01/equipping-kingdom-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2017/11/01/equipping-kingdom-workers/</guid>
      <description>Missionary Care Workshop A few weeks ago, Jolanda, as part of the YWAM North American Member Care Network, was asked to give a workshop on missionary care at a YWAM conference here in Colorado Springs.
 For the most part, this conference focused on people who are doing a Discipleship Training School (DTS) at the moment. The conference was attended by about 200 students from different YWAM locations (from various states).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is bear-y good!</title>
      <link>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2017/09/04/this-is-bear-y-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://focused-bhabha-6e5ce0.netlify.com/en/updates/2017/09/04/this-is-bear-y-good/</guid>
      <description>Ever been awakened in the middle of the night by a bear trying to get into your trash can, but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in? This has happened to us a couple of times, but the most recent time, we finally got to see the bear live and in person. Thankfully, we have a chain on our trash can that kept him (her?) out, and once he saw us peeking out of the window at him, he ran away, but not before we got a look at him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>