<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on The Blevins</title>
    <link>https://zending.us/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on The Blevins</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zending.us/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing in Missionaries</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/updates/2019/03/19/investing-in-missionaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/updates/2019/03/19/investing-in-missionaries/</guid>
      <description>Jo&amp;rsquo;s time in Pennsylvania Jolanda has put another notch in her belt, aka visited yet another, new state. Before you know it, she will have visited more states than Rodney!
She had a great time visiting an area where Amish and Mennonites live. The debriefing retreat for missionaries was held in Lancaster County, Pennsylvania, in the pretty town of Ephrata. What a different world than Colorado! The rolling hills reminded her a lot of Germany and Luxembourg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debriefing in Pennsylvania</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/updates/2019/02/09/debriefing-in-pennsylvania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/updates/2019/02/09/debriefing-in-pennsylvania/</guid>
      <description>Snow Everywhere It&amp;rsquo;s been a snowy January, here in the US and in The Netherlands. It was on a snowy day in January six years ago that we packed our 9 suitcases in a van and headed for the airport for our flight to Colorado. We can hardly believe it ourselves, but January 26th marked our 6 anniversary here in the US. My how the time has flown.
 A couple of weeks ago, during an unexpected snowstorm, Jolanda tried to bring Sarah to school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help! We have a freshman and a middle-schooler!</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/updates/2018/09/27/help-we-have-a-freshman-and-a-middle-schooler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/updates/2018/09/27/help-we-have-a-freshman-and-a-middle-schooler/</guid>
      <description>22-year missions adventure This month marks 22 years ago that we went into missions and started our Youth with a Mission adventure.
An incredible missionary adventure with God, an adventure in faith and trust, an adventure across borders, an adventure in being dependent on donations, an adventure in wonderful provision, blessings and testimonies. 22 years of missions made possible, in part, by you!
 First missions trip to Uganda in 1996.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministry Partners Wanted</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/ministry-partners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/ministry-partners/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;I felt completely heard and understood&#34;</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/updates/2018/05/17/i-felt-completely-heard-and-understood/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/updates/2018/05/17/i-felt-completely-heard-and-understood/</guid>
      <description>The last week of April and the first week of May, seven participants came for the &amp;ldquo;Radiant Life&amp;rdquo; Debriefing retreat for missionary families, couples and singles in Orlando. This was a period of rest, refreshment and renewal for these missionaries. Here are just a couple of powerful testimonies from participants in the Radiant Life debriefing retreat in Orlando, Florida:
&amp;ldquo;What a week! Our family spent the last 9 days in Florida attending a missionary debrief conference “Radiant Life” through Excelling Leaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/about-us/</guid>
      <description>We, Rodney and Jolanda Blevins, have been missionaries with Youth With A Mission (YWAM) since 1997. Through various missions and ministry trips throughout the years, we have impacted people in 16 different countries spanning five continents!
We both did a Discipleship Training School (DTS) at the YWAM base Heidebeek in Heerde, The Netherlands. The DTS is YWAM’s six month training course designed to help you understand God more deeply, live more like Jesus and identify your unique gifts and purpose to use in missions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missionaries not just surviving, but thriving!</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/updates/2018/02/26/missionaries-not-just-surviving-but-thriving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/updates/2018/02/26/missionaries-not-just-surviving-but-thriving/</guid>
      <description>International Member Care Consultation (IMCC) A couple weeks ago Jolanda attended the International Member Care Consultation (IMCC) at YWAM Orlando, FL. Together with YWAM Member Care workers from the Caribbean, East and South East Asia, Europe, North America, South America and Africa they came together to reconnect, receive teaching, and do a lot of networking. It was a great opportunity to learn about the different training models/courses and internships for member care workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipping Kingdom Workers</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/updates/2017/11/01/equipping-kingdom-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/updates/2017/11/01/equipping-kingdom-workers/</guid>
      <description>Missionary Care Workshop A few weeks ago, Jolanda, as part of the YWAM North American Member Care Network, was asked to give a workshop on missionary care at a YWAM conference here in Colorado Springs.
 For the most part, this conference focused on people who are doing a Discipleship Training School (DTS) at the moment. The conference was attended by about 200 students from different YWAM locations (from various states).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is bear-y good!</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/updates/2017/09/04/this-is-bear-y-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/updates/2017/09/04/this-is-bear-y-good/</guid>
      <description>Ever been awakened in the middle of the night by a bear trying to get into your trash can, but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in? This has happened to us a couple of times, but the most recent time, we finally got to see the bear live and in person. Thankfully, we have a chain on our trash can that kept him (her?) out, and once he saw us peeking out of the window at him, he ran away, but not before we got a look at him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Values of YWAM</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/faq/values-of-ywam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/faq/values-of-ywam/</guid>
      <description>Youth With A Mission (YWAM) affirms the Bible as the authoritative word of God and, with the Holy Spirit’s inspiration, the absolute reference point for every aspect of life and ministry. Based upon God’s word, who He is, and His initiative of salvation, the following responses are strongly emphasized in YWAM:
Worship: We are called to praise and worship God alone
Holiness: We are called to lead holy and righteous lives that exemplify the nature and character of God</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What we believe</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/faq/what-we-believe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/faq/what-we-believe/</guid>
      <description>We strongly believe that the truth of the Gospel applied to every area of society – Family, Church, Education, Media, Celebration (art, entertainment, sport) Business (which starts with innovations in science and technology, productivity, sales, and service), and Government is the only way to transform a nation. Only Christian values and principles based on godly truth will be the way to walk into the inheritance that Nations have in the kingdom of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who is YWAM?</title>
      <link>https://zending.us/en/faq/who-is-ywam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zending.us/en/faq/who-is-ywam/</guid>
      <description>Youth With A Mission (YWAM) encompasses thousands of people and hundreds of ministries in almost every country of the world. In every case, our passion is to know God and to make Him known.
We are a mixture of people from all over the world, from over 130 countries including places like Indonesia, Nepal and Mozambique. In many of our locations, people from a wide variety of nations serve side by side.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>