<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on In English</title>
    <link>https://en.blevins.nl/update/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on In English</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://en.blevins.nl/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Missionaries not just surviving, but thriving!</title>
      <link>https://en.blevins.nl/2018/02/26/missionaries-not-just-surviving-but-thriving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.blevins.nl/2018/02/26/missionaries-not-just-surviving-but-thriving/</guid>
      <description>International Member Care Consultation (IMCC) A couple weeks ago Jolanda attended the International Member Care Consultation (IMCC) at YWAM Orlando, FL. Together with YWAM Member Care workers from the Caribbean, East and South East Asia, Europe, North America, South America and Africa they came together to reconnect, receive teaching, and do a lot of networking. It was a great opportunity to learn about the different training models/courses and internships for member care workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipping Kingdom Workers</title>
      <link>https://en.blevins.nl/2017/11/01/equipping-kingdom-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.blevins.nl/2017/11/01/equipping-kingdom-workers/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, Jolanda, as part of the YWAM North American Member Care Network, was asked to give a…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is bear-y good!</title>
      <link>https://en.blevins.nl/2017/09/04/this-is-bear-y-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.blevins.nl/2017/09/04/this-is-bear-y-good/</guid>
      <description>Ever been awakened in the middle of the night by a bear trying to get into your trash can, but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in? This has happened to us a couple of times, but the most recent time, we finally got to see the bear live and in person. Thankfully, we have a chain on our trash can that kept him (her?) out, and once he saw us peeking out of the window at him, he ran away, but not before we got a look at him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We komen eraan!</title>
      <link>https://en.blevins.nl/2017/05/01/we-komen-eraan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 21:55:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://en.blevins.nl/2017/05/01/we-komen-eraan/</guid>
      <description>De laatste schoolweek van de meiden is aangebroken en dit schooljaar is bijna afgesloten.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>